// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one of these has a different meaning from the rest?",
    answer: "Tiny",
    options: [
      "Huge",
      "Massive",
      "Gigantic",
      "Tiny"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which adjective best completes this sentence? \"Whose ___ new car is that?\"",
    answer: "Shiny",
    options: [
      "Rich",
      "Shiny",
      "Slim",
      "Yummy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of these is NOT related to taste?",
    answer: "Humid",
    options: [
      "Sour",
      "Humid",
      "Sweet",
      "Bitter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Andrea lives next door so we _____ see her.",
    answer: "Often",
    options: [
      "Rarely",
      "Never",
      "Often",
      "Occasionally"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "We meet _____ at the Annual General Meeting",
    answer: "Yearly",
    options: [
      "Yearly",
      "Every day",
      "Never",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "It [0%] _____ rains here in the summer.",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Always",
      "Rarely",
      "Sometimes",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 7,
    question: "A single unit of rice is known as a",
    answer: "Grain",
    options: [
      "Gram",
      "Grain",
      "Drop",
      "Rice"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Wich of the following is the correct phrase a group of insects",
    answer: "A swarm of insects",
    options: [
      "A flock of insects",
      "A swarm of insects",
      "A school of insects",
      "A shoal of insects"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Choose the most appropriate answer and fill in the blanks.The noun form of\'Do\'is______",
    answer: "Deed",
    options: [
      "Does",
      "Deed",
      "Done",
      "Did"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "She spoke too softly.I couldn't____________her.",
    answer: "Hear",
    options: [
      "Hear",
      "Heared",
      "Here",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "We went shopping and I ______________ a new pair of jeans.",
    answer: "Bought",
    options: [
      "Buy",
      "Have Bought",
      "Bought",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Fill in the blanks with the appropriate form of the verb. I () Present",
    answer: "eat",
    options: [
      "eat",
      "Eated",
      "Eaten",
      "Non"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Fill in the blanks with the appropriate form of the verb. I (Eat) Past",
    answer: "ate",
    options: [
      "eat",
      "ate",
      "have eat ",
      "has eaten"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "As part of my new job, I get (meals partly paid for by the company).Replace the words in parentheses with a word or phrase with a similar meaning",
    answer: "subsidised meals",
    options: [
      "role",
      "salary",
      "subsidised meals ",
      "healthcare"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "You should only apply for the job if you have (led a team before).",
    answer: "leadership qualities",
    options: [
      "benefits package",
      "ubsidised",
      "full training",
      "leadership qualities"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Working in the factory over the summer gave me some (direct) experience of manufacturing.Replace the words in parentheses with a word or phrase with a similar meaning",
    answer: "hands-on",
    options: [
      "hands-on",
      "openings ",
      "Ate",
      "online application"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "I'm afraid you'll have to (speak up / eye up / head up). I can hardly hear what you're saying.",
    answer: "speak up",
    options: [
      "eye up",
      "speak up",
      "head up",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "We are (taking / recruiting / searching) people for our new branch in the city centre.choose the right word",
    answer: "recruiting",
    options: [
      "recruiting",
      "taking",
      "searching",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "We'd better (_____________) on if weâ€™re going to get to the hostel before dark.Complete the sentences with a verb, using the appropriate form.",
    answer: "rush",
    options: [
      "come up against",
      "ubsidised",
      "put forward",
      "rush"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "I'm going to (_____________) on after work to finish the report.Complete the sentences with a verb, using the appropriate form.",
    answer: "pressed on",
    options: [
      "going on",
      "pressed on",
      "brush up on",
      "put together"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];